
Starting copy...
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 1000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 2000

2599 rows copied.
Network packet size (bytes): 4096
Clock Time (ms.) Total     : 16     Average : (162437.50 rows per sec.)

Starting copy...
SQLState = S1000, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Warning: BCP import with a format file will convert empty strings in delimited columns to NULL.
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 1000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 2000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 3000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 4000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 5000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 6000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 7000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 8000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 9000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 10000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 11000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 12000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 13000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 14000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 15000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 16000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 17000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 18000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 19000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 20000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 21000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 22000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 23000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 24000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 25000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 26000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 27000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 28000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 29000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 30000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 31000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 32000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 33000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 34000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 35000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 36000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 37000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 38000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 39000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 40000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 41000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 42000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 43000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 44000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 45000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 46000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 47000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 48000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 49000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 50000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 51000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 52000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 53000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 54000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 55000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 56000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 57000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 58000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 59000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 60000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 61000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 62000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 63000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 64000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 65000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 66000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 67000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 68000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 69000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 70000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 71000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 72000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 73000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 74000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 75000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 76000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 77000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 78000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 79000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 80000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 81000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 82000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 83000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 84000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 85000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 86000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 87000

87984 rows copied.
Network packet size (bytes): 4096
Clock Time (ms.) Total     : 406    Average : (216709.36 rows per sec.)

Starting copy...
SQLState = S1000, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Warning: BCP import with a format file will convert empty strings in delimited columns to NULL.
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 1000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 2000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 3000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 4000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 5000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 6000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 7000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 8000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 9000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 10000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 11000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 12000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 13000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 14000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 15000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 16000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 17000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 18000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 19000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 20000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 21000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 22000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 23000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 24000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 25000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 26000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 27000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 28000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 29000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 30000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 31000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 32000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 33000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 34000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 35000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 36000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 37000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 38000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 39000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 40000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 41000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 42000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 43000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 44000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 45000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 46000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 47000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 48000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 49000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 50000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 51000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 52000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 53000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 54000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 55000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 56000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 57000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 58000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 59000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 60000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 61000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 62000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 63000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 64000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 65000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 66000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 67000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 68000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 69000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 70000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 71000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 72000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 73000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 74000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 75000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 76000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 77000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 78000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 79000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 80000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 81000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 82000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 83000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 84000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 85000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 86000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 87000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 88000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 89000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 90000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 91000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 92000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 93000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 94000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 95000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 96000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 97000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 98000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 99000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 100000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 101000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 102000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 103000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 104000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 105000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 106000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 107000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 108000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 109000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 110000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 111000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 112000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 113000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 114000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 115000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 116000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 117000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 118000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 119000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 120000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 121000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 122000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 123000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 124000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 125000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 126000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 127000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 128000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 129000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 130000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 131000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 132000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 133000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 134000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 135000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 136000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 137000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 138000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 139000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 140000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 141000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 142000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 143000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 144000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 145000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 146000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 147000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 148000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 149000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 150000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 151000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 152000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 153000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 154000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 155000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 156000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 157000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 158000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 159000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 160000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 161000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 162000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 163000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 164000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 165000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 166000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 167000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 168000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 169000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 170000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 171000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 172000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 173000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 174000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 175000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 176000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 177000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 178000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 179000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 180000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 181000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 182000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 183000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 184000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 185000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 186000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 187000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 188000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 189000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 190000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 191000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 192000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 193000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 194000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 195000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 196000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 197000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 198000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 199000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 200000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 201000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 202000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 203000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 204000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 205000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 206000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 207000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 208000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 209000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 210000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 211000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 212000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 213000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 214000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 215000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 216000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 217000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 218000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 219000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 220000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 221000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 222000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 223000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 224000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 225000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 226000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 227000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 228000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 229000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 230000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 231000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 232000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 233000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 234000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 235000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 236000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 237000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 238000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 239000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 240000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 241000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 242000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 243000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 244000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 245000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 246000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 247000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 248000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 249000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 250000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 251000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 252000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 253000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 254000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 255000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 256000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 257000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 258000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 259000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 260000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 261000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 262000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 263000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 264000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 265000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 266000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 267000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 268000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 269000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 270000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 271000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 272000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 273000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 274000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 275000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 276000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 277000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 278000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 279000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 280000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 281000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 282000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 283000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 284000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 285000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 286000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 287000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 288000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 289000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 290000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 291000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 292000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 293000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 294000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 295000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 296000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 297000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 298000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 299000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 300000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 301000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 302000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 303000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 304000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 305000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 306000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 307000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 308000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 309000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 310000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 311000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 312000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 313000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 314000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 315000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 316000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 317000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 318000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 319000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 320000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 321000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 322000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 323000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 324000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 325000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 326000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 327000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 328000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 329000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 330000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 331000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 332000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 333000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 334000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 335000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 336000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 337000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 338000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 339000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 340000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 341000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 342000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 343000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 344000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 345000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 346000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 347000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 348000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 349000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 350000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 351000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 352000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 353000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 354000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 355000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 356000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 357000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 358000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 359000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 360000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 361000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 362000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 363000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 364000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 365000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 366000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 367000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 368000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 369000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 370000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 371000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 372000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 373000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 374000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 375000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 376000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 377000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 378000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 379000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 380000

380797 rows copied.
Network packet size (bytes): 4096
Clock Time (ms.) Total     : 1172   Average : (324912.13 rows per sec.)

Starting copy...
SQLState = S1000, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Warning: BCP import with a format file will convert empty strings in delimited columns to NULL.
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 1000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 2000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 3000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 4000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 5000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 6000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 7000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 8000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 9000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 10000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 11000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 12000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 13000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 14000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 15000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 16000

16966 rows copied.
Network packet size (bytes): 4096
Clock Time (ms.) Total     : 31     Average : (547290.31 rows per sec.)
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a connection to SQL Server [1326]. 
SQLState = 08001, NativeError = 1326
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]A network-related or instance-specific error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server. Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections. For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
SQLState = S1T00, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Login timeout expired

Starting copy...
SQLState = S1000, NativeError = 0
Error = [Microsoft][ODBC Driver 13 for SQL Server]Warning: BCP import with a format file will convert empty strings in delimited columns to NULL.
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 1000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 2000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 3000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 4000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 5000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 6000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 7000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 8000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 9000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 10000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 11000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 12000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 13000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 14000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 15000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 16000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 17000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 18000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 19000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 20000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 21000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 22000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 23000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 24000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 25000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 26000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 27000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 28000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 29000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 30000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 31000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 32000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 33000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 34000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 35000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 36000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 37000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 38000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 39000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 40000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 41000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 42000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 43000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 44000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 45000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 46000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 47000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 48000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 49000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 50000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 51000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 52000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 53000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 54000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 55000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 56000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 57000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 58000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 59000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 60000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 61000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 62000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 63000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 64000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 65000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 66000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 67000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 68000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 69000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 70000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 71000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 72000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 73000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 74000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 75000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 76000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 77000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 78000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 79000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 80000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 81000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 82000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 83000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 84000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 85000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 86000
1000 rows successfully bulk-copied to host-file. Total received: 87000

87984 rows copied.
Network packet size (bytes): 4096
Clock Time (ms.) Total     : 453    Average : (194225.17 rows per sec.)
